[ar: tobyMac]
[ti: I just need U.]
[al: I just need U.]
[by: BRYAN98]
[length: 03:46]
[id: qwzsqvck]
[Verse 1]
[00:08.81]Last night put the heavy on me
[00:11.87]Woke up and I'm feeling lonely
[00:14.12]This world gotta a way of showing me (showing me)
[00:18.24]Some days it'll lift you up
[00:20.99]Some days it'll call your bluff
[00:23.18]Man, most of my days I ain't got enough

[Pre-Chorus 1]
[00:27.81]And all I know
[00:32.81]Is You're my only hope

[Chorus]
[00:37.18]When I’m up when I’m down (uh, huh)
[00:40.06]When the wolves come around (tell me)
[00:42.37]When my feet hit the ground
[00:44.31]I just need, I just need You
[00:47.25]On my darkest days (uh, huh)
[00:49.31]When I'm losing faith (tell me)
[00:52.01]No, it ain't gon' change
[00:53.45]I just need, I just need You
[01:02.46]Lord, I need You
[01:12.86]Yeah, I just need You

[Post-Chorus]
[01:12.96]Yeah, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death
[01:17.00]I will fear no evil, for Thou art with me
[01:21.19]Thy rod and thy staff

[Verse 2]
[01:23.39]They comfort me when I'm beat down, broken
[01:25.46]Hold my heart when it's split right wide open
[01:27.46]Turn these eyes to my Soul Protector
[01:29.42]Break the will of this born infector

[Pre-Chorus 1]
[01:33.12]Cuz' all I know, all I know
[01:36.93]Is You're my only hope

[Chorus]
[01:41.52]When I’m up when I’m down (uh, huh)
[01:44.33]When the wolves come around (tell me)
[01:47.02]When my feet hit the ground
[01:47.93]I just need, I just need You
[01:51.62]On my darkest days (uh, huh)
[01:53.61]When I'm losing faith (tell me)
[01:56.18]No, it ain't gon' change
[01:57.13]I just need, I just need You
[02:08.51]Lord, I need You
[02:17.71]Yeah, I just need You

[Bridge]
[02:19.59]When You pull me closer, I come to life
[02:22.90]When You pull me closer, I come to life
[02:27.34]When You pull me closer, I come to life
[02:32.11]When You pull me closer, I come to life
[02:36.36]
[Pre-Chorus 2]
[02:38.11]When I’m up when I’m down
[02:40.05]When my feet hit the ground
[02:45.42]On my darkest days
[02:49.00]No, it ain't gon' change
[02:53.86]Oh Lord, I need You
[02:56.74]
[Chorus]
[02:58.42]When the wolves come around
[02:58.96]When I’m up when I’m down
[03:00.11]When my feet hit the ground
[03:02.29]Yeah, I need, I need, I need, I need You
[03:05.29]On my darkest days
[03:08.04]When I'm losing faith
[03:10.17]No, it ain't gon' change
[03:12.04]Ain't no way this thing gon' change, it's You
[03:14.42]
[Outro]
[03:16.48]Is You, I need
[03:18.29]Is You, I need
[03:19.54]On my darkest days
[03:20.60]When I'm losing faith
[03:21.80]I need You, I need, Is You, I need
[03:28.12]Every single day, every breath I take
[03:31.17]I need You, I need You